My high school student detective Shinichi Kudo
At the amusement park where I went to play with my childhood friend Ran
I witnessed a suspicious
deal of men in black clothes.
And they dope me
My body got smaller
When it turns out that
Shinichi Kudo is alive,
I think he'll hurt the
people around him
In the name of Edogawa Conan
Gathering information from the black organization
Anyone who knows who I am
With Dr. Agatha
Classmate Haibara Aida
Her real name is Shiho Miyano
She is part of a black organization
and her codename is Sherry
I am the developer of
APTX4869 that made me small
Her older sister is murdered and all caught
trying to run away from her organization.
After she took the medicine herself
She lives under
the name Haibara Ai
She is working on an antidote
But all she found
out was APTX4869
If you use the ingredients of alcohol
It is only that she can temporarily
return to her original body.
Even if the body gets smaller,
the brain stays the same!
The truth is always one!
And this
This is the most recent story.
Smells like
"Black tissue, Jin"
The smell?
"Black Tissue, Walker"
It's the smell of a woman who betrayed us.
On a night like tonight
I have a feeling of meeting
Sherry, you mean
"Miss Japeresque
Award Celebration Party"
Awesome
-At the Suzuki tycoon Bellwood Hotel
.-Nice hotel.
Held in commemoration of the opening
Miss Japeresque
Winner celebration
party is coming soon
cool
There are many famous people, right?
Isn't it like a Suzuki chaebol?
This is a really nice hotel
right?
"The Haibara child"
You now
'I want to see you someday with Shinichi'
-Did you think so?
- Huh?
no
I thought I wanted to come with Conan.
-Right, Conan?
- Huh
Both are the same
A little boy like this is a
hotel, it's a million years fast.
Sonoko, this guy
Huh?
Who is Kogoro?
That's what
"Material, whereabouts,
personal credit, corporate credit..."
What?  what?
"Detective, Kogoro Mori"
You can meet Miss Japeresque?
To Mr. Karen Kotobuki,
Miss Japeresque of the Year
Crowned
Karen
beautiful
So where?
Where can he meet?
Hotel newly built at Sonokone House
A lot of famous people come
The party is also broadcast live.
Right
If famous people gather
This excellent detective has
solved many difficult cases
Mori Kogoro is indispensable
excuse me
I am the one who solves the case.
I can't help it
I need to meet you
I'll change into a tuxedo
Dad, wait a minute
Even if Karen falls in love
with me, it's not my fault.
this!
No, we will meet!
-I rolled on the stairs and broke my leg
.-I'm seeing Karen!
No, no
Mr. Karen
We will meet
He says he has to
relax in the hospital now.
So instead, I and my child came
I don’t have time to change clothes
Would it be okay to dress like this?
It's okay, it doesn't matter
Ran is cute no matter what you wear
Go
Why did you come to me?
I know that?  Women
She sees a beautiful woman
and how to take care of herself
What?
Mr. Sonoko
Thank you very much today
It's Mr. Mimi, the older sister
of Mr. Karen, Miss Japeresque.
"Karen's sister Mimi Kotobuki"
that...
Her sister got a blackmail letter.
"Kotobuki Karen's waiting room"
Lovely karen
Congratulations on the award
'Tonight, through your heart'
'I'll make it my puppet doll'
'If you disobey,
there is only'death'
I found it under the door a little while ago
Even the staff only know a few
Sweet smell
It’s dangerous if you do this
-Come on, the police..
.-You don't have to.
see
If you come, tell me to come
It’s an honor that I earned
by trying hard enough to die.
You can't lose to
this cowardly guy
How do I add 10 times more?
Sorry
Well, it's a peculiar
taste, but it's not tasteless
It's okay, just let it go
Yeah
Here you go
looks delicious
Little kids cake
Anyway, she's a stagnant woman
Karen is
But you don’t even know where
the pervert who sent the letter is.
Ran, call your husband.
To Shinichi Kudo
Ran, please
Huh
I don't get it
Shinichi?
Mr. Karen, Miss Japeresque,
got a blackmail letter.
If you can come...
Your precious ran is in a dangerous situation
Come to the Bellwood
Hotel right now, okay?
Sonoko, Shinichi is busy
If you don't come
even if you do this
I don't need a man who
can't even contact you
still
What are you gonna do?
It would be better to call me
I see
"Suzuki conglomerate Bellwood Hotel
Miss Japeresque award commemoration...
Kudo
Haibara
Is it the cake?
Yes, that taste was fed to you before
Goryangju and liqueur are in it
Haibara, quickly
Your body is hot and your
body will go back to normal
"Women's changing room"
Haibara, are you okay?
Sorry
I broke the women's
locker room key
Rather, what are you going to do?
If it is like this, your body will grow bigger
Haibara
"Miss Japeresque
Award Celebration Party"
Then please
Good morning
-Hello
.-Thank you.
I'm white
You change
"Jun Miss Abe Sumika"
You said you're
wearing a black dress
I changed my mind when I saw the light color
Go fast
"Jun Miss Kawada Kyomi"
Don't do this
You can't see my necklace
This is a gift from mom
I will never subtract
-Karen, do it in moderation
.-Miura, are you a judge?
It's a miss given by a
kid like this, so cancel it.
please
"Chairman of the
jury, Daigo Miura"
Will you release it?
Karen asked me to
stand in front of me...
Are you saying you only need to stand out?
"Stage Director Shoichi Amano"
10 minutes left
-Hurry up to the lighting tea
m-Yes
Lighting director, please change
Suzuki Conglomerate Bell
Wood Hotel Opening Ceremony
The Miss Japeresque
Awards Ceremony begins.
Are they too late?
-The little ones must be playing well
.-First
This is the appearance of the
two of Jun Miss Japeresque.
This is Sumika Abe
and Kyomi Kawada.
You've been waiting a lot
Glorious Miss
Japeresque Inn of the Year
This is Karen Kotobuki.
Camera 3, follow well
light!
Today is a new beginning for me
Be sure to reach the
top in world competitions
I think it is my role to
promote the beauty of Japan
To the managers who held such
a wonderful celebration party...
-Yes, this is Agatha
.-Thank you very much.
-Shinichi?
-If you are speaking like this
-I can feel your heart
.-Trust me, I'll pick you up now.
Doctor?
Come find the child lost.
-Then me to
o-No, it's okay
You are here
Are you really a kid?
Please don't
stare at me, doctor.
No, I knew from theory
Seeing it in person like this,
it looks like the first person
then
It's been a while
Shinichi
Thanks, Doctor.
I almost became a woman's dress
Regret
I wanted to see you dressed up
-It'll go well with you
.-Noisy.
What's more, Shinichi
It’s the same as when I
accidentally drank goryangju
Because the alcohol component works
It's back to normal
In other words, Haibara
who came back to this form
You shouldn’t expose
it to many people
Please take me right to your house.
But that's the same
for you, Shinichi
I can't go
Are you going to meet
even your lovely lover?
Fool
Because of the blackmail letter.
Until the party is over
I will stay here
It is unclear how much the liqueur
effect of the cake we ate will last
I don't know when I'll return to being a child
-I know
.-Then
Even if you know it's a dangerous situation
Not running away from the case in front of you
It's the basics of a detective.
-Please take care of Haibara
.-Yes.
This is for disguise
then...
Then shall we go too?
First, Mr. Karen
How did you feel when
the award was decided?
So far
-First 30 minute
s-It seemed to be rewarded
Miss Japeresque on the stage
In the meantime, we investigate hotel structure.
Is there any suspicious place
"Kotobuki Karen's waiting room"
On the 20th floor
Kotobuki Karen's
waiting room is locked.
Opposite is the judges' room.
It's easy to see what kind of relationship it is.
The 10th floor is the waiting room for Miss June
Only the staff with the
pass can enter the stage
If the blackmail letter is true
How to approach it
I would like a big applause
to all of Miss Japeresque.
And decorating the end
Miss Japeresque
Kotobuki Karen's specialty
Playing the piano
Excuse me
What would you like to drink?
cool
-I'll use juice
.-Okay
What is it?
I'm okay
I'll go find the children
You did a good job with this dress too
If you do what I say, I will
make you the best in the world
happy
Karen
Why did you change your speech?
Please listen to me
Noisy
Don't tell me you're an older sister
Because I’m sorry, I have the manager
Mr. Karen, please wait
under the stage at 8:45.
I know
Pretend to be a queen
but I can't do anything alone
It's like a puppet doll
Puppet doll?
"Puppet doll"
Like the blackmail letter
It would be nice if
you were really bad
Mr. Kyomi
Mr. Amano actually thinks so
Since the rehearsal, the order
has changed several times
Because that’s my job.
Elevator
Conan
Child
Doctor
Conan
Child
Shinichi?
Shinichi
Shinichi, right?
You can tell just by looking at your hand gestures
right
It's me
Shinichi
I barely met
barely
Fool
why are you crying
Where have you been so far?
I was worried
I miss you
Ran
What do we do?
Without seeing
I gained weight
It's very bad
And it turns out that my waist
awhile
It's been a long time since
we met you, what's that mean
That is unfair!
This is more like you
Well, I'll see you
Did you come here after hearing a voice message?
Yeah, so I'm looking
into the hotel right now
Rather, why are
you running around?
Conan and Ai seem to be lost.
They said earlier that the
doctor will take you home?
like that
then
I want to investigate together
What?
there
- How old are you?
-I'm working right now.
-I'm sorry
.-Do you have a girlfriend?
Karen?
Karen, are you inside?
Answer me
-What a fus
s-Don't be pretentious
You have a younger sister again?
Karen always said that
She's choking her
with her gloomy sister
Did she say everything?
What's going on?
Who are you?
Detective
Detective?
I’m Mori Kogoro’s assistant.
Yes it's true
Did Karen disappear?
-This guy has it
.-You said you didn't know.
right
Shall I appeal my
resentment to the detective?
Come on in
Not in this room
in case
Can I check out Karen's room?
Yes, as you please
-Ran, look at the bathroom
.-Yes.
no
When did Karen disappear?
A little while ago
I said I'd wash it before
putting on the next dress
It disappeared after I opened my eyes for a moment.
What dress to wear next?
Disappeared
And a belt worn under the dress.
Belt underneath?
Karen
She at the end she'll appear
like an angel under the stage
It's like a belt, to lift
her body in the air...
Anyway, I’ll look for it before the main show.
Unfortunately, if you have an
older sister who is so watchful
Karen is just a puppet
-A puppet doll?
- okay
But she's a pro
She'll show up just in time
No worries
What are you gonna do, Shinichi?
Let's find Karen
Ran pleases her chairman
I can’t go out in
front of people
Ok
Karen?
She didn't see
Thank you
-What about Karen?
-She hasn't found it yet.
"A waiting area under the stage, stage equipment"
here is?
It's a waiting area under the stage
Karen uses this to go
up in the air on stage
It was Miura, the judges, who
thought about directing this way
Miura is trying to
control her little brother
I have to protect
Control...
Karen didn't come with you?
She, too, did she not come here?
Is she also doing what she wants?
It will come 15 minutes
to the main broadcast.
I'm going this way and
you're going to be there
what
You can tell me your age
Karen, you are ready.
Finally appeared
Yeah
thank God
Excuse me, thank you
Mr. Amano, the stage director
Karen is waiting
under the stage.
This is bothering me
I struggled to find it, then...
You've been waiting for a long time
This is Miss Japeresque Kotobuki
Karen's piano performance.
It's late
I have a job
What is that
I didn't direct it like this
Did you do it?
No
in a bad mood
It's a perfect puppet doll
What happened
Dead
Turn the camera!
Let's advertise, advertise!
-Doctor
.-Sorry, Ichi Shin.
A little bit in the middle of a glance
Listen carefully,
please stop here
It's a murder case, please!
No, you can't go out
-No
.-Shinichi
found
Why are you back?
I came to get the cake
If you investigate the ingredients
What are you doing?
You were shot on a live broadcast
This live broadcast has an audience rating of about 20%
In a fifth probability
You let the black gang
know where you are
Run away from here as quickly as possible anyway
Hate
I can't miss this opportunity
How long are you
going to be a child?
Don't you want to go
back to Shinichi Kudo?
Shinichi?
What are you doing?
It has nothing to do with you
Wait a minute, it doesn't matter
You mean, do you know
how long Ran waited?
I barely wanted to show up,
but I was stuck with another girl.
Somebody help me
anyway
I don't have time to explain
Understand?  Run away
What, really
I think you resemble that person
I wanted to meet you, Sherry.
As always
Please keep it a secret that I
cooperate with the investigation.
I see if you say that.
The culprit
The victim's limbs and
waist were tied with strings.
The string was cut and fell
Is it murder
Yes maybe
Victim got a blackmail letter.
This knife
She had it for self-defense.
Inspector
This is a blackmail letter.
'Tonight, I'll pierce your
heart and make it my puppet'
The appearance of her body
It was the puppet itself.
To pierce your heart means
to put a knife in your heart
This is a planned murder
tailored to a blackmail letter.
According to consensus, the estimated time of
death seems to be between 8:30 and 9 o'clock.
8:45
There were no bodies under the stage.
Excuse me, Lieutenant.
You last checked the victim?
Yes, on stage 3 minutes
before the main broadcast...
"Miss Japeresque
Award Celebration Party"
Mr. Karen, we're starting soon.
Are you ready?
Did you start broadcasting
even though you didn't answer?
It was common that
Mr. Karen didn’t answer,
I would have died
The time the crime took place
8:45 to 8:57
For 12 minutes.
In the meantime, it means the
person without an alibi is the culprit
No matter how, this
way of killing is too much.
Excuse me
-Ye
s-Is it Shinichi?
Yeah
I'm insisting that my
child won't go back
"Jilbei Gin, Vodka"
Haibara
The amount eaten is also different
We had symptoms
almost at the same time.
Maybe it has to do
with gender differences.
I need a sample somehow
-Go quickl
y-Shinichi
You said it was dangerous
with a fifth chance
This is also a four-fifth chance
We are a community of destiny
Run away together
We have to investigate
There is no other way
Ran
sorry
The doctor told me to bring
the car because it was ready.
Haibara
Ran
I'll explain the situation
later. It's an emergency.
I'm sorry, but take
him to your place.
please
Ok
Can you give me your name?
No. Is there any reason?
No, this guy
-Hi..
.-Hi Lee
I'm mixed race, please.
I'm Mori Ran
there
Where have you met?
I feel like someone I know
Ok?
I'm not sure about that
Is it too?
Then see you later, Shinichi
Your car is over there.
Go
Why are you?
What, that person
-Doctor
.-Yes.
Have you been there yet?
Somebody aimed at Mr. Hyri with a knife.
Ran protected
awhile
Are those guys
I think I'm already surrounded
Moving with those two people
I can't get it involved
The moment you drop your knife
I lost your life too
What are you going to do now?
He's a rat in a poison.
There's no need to rush.
It's fun to drive him up little by little
Sherry
I can see your trembling back
Haibara?
Feel it
I can feel their
presence right up close
Who is that person
Doctor, do you know something?
That's what
I've heard of one assistant
Maybe not that person?
He didn’t tell me
he had an assistant.
That is
And I just spoke with a
serious face to Mr. Hyri.
I've never seen such a scary face
I think Shinichi has become
someone I don't know
Shinichi no matter what happens
Nothing has changed
What to do if Ran doesn't believe
I'm already caught by
the muzzle of the tissue
All that's left is waiting
for the trigger to be pulled
Your weak look is not like you
At least it's safe while the police are there
After that, I will protect it
You too
Can I ask for one?
If there is danger to me
Don't hesitate and throw it away
Fool
Don't be bullshit
What is a detective
Even if it’s annoying evidence
that interferes with reasoning,
Do not throw away
I'll reason properly and
solve the case brilliantly.
Rest assured
Kudo, there were no
prints on the weapon knife.
And gathered people
who don't have alibi
Okay
What about this lady?
It's like my assistant.
then
For 12 minutes from 8:45 to
3 minutes before broadcast
Let me know where you did what
From you
I was looking for my younger brother
Who can someone prove it?
You are Karen's manager,
The relationship was pretty bad.
I think of my brother.
You?
I was still in the room
I was making a business phone call.
You can check it out
If you have an accomplice, murder is possible.
No alibi.
And you seem to have been
pretty obsessed with Mr. Karen.
As Karen keeps you away
Didn't hate arise as much as
you had a deep heart to be pretty?
I beg your pardon?
Jun Miss, Mr. Sumika Abe
Where are you?
I've been in Kyomi's room all the time
The two hated Karen.
And Karen disappears
The biggest benefit
One of two people who are June misses.
Two people working together
It's also possible that
he murdered Karen.
Stage director Shoichi Amano
At 8:45
After confirming that
Mr. Karen is not under the stage,
After that, adjust the
equipment in the basement
I wonder if Karen has come.
I've been going down
the stage a few times
in short
There is no perfect alibi.
What...
But I have no
motivation to kill Karen.
Don't belittle the police
You are Karen's ex-boyfriend.
Belonged to the same small theater
group and had the same dream
But it seems like a
big difference now.
I was glad she was successful
Really
Found it
No, not yet
Get ready
When the police withdraw
Then I start hunting
What is this feeling?
Somewhere different from when I came before
And I feel one more
sense of difference
'I'll make it my puppet doll'
Is it your job?
It's a perfect puppet doll
What happened?
I don't know what it is
Take a look at this
The bloodstain
It runs from the entrance to that side
Inspector Megure
Please check right away
if this blood is the victim.
okay
If this is her blood
Killed it somewhere
else and moved it here.
Why did you do something so annoying?
First hypothesis
To execute planned murder
Killing here is too dangerous
I don't know when the
staff will come to find Karen.
So after killing in another place
Quickly made of a puppet doll.
What is the second hypothesis?
To hide the real murder scene
What is it?
No, something caught on me
Go
Now, this is the key to Karen's room.
Where are the keys to the other room?
The only things I handed were Miura-san,
Sumika-san, Kyomi-san, and the three room keys.
Other keys are strictly
managed by the hotel.
I see, thank you
What is it, he
I can't help it
Because if you immerse yourself in
Shinichi's case, nothing else can be seen.
Ran, understanding everything
is not just being gentle
Because there is also a
kindness that is arbitrary
I'm fine
When the case is resolved, I
will speak with Shinichi properly.
Do not worry about it
Okay, let's go
But what was that?
Haibara
Don't go around alone in the hotel
Is it time to worry about me?
I'm struggling only with my presence
He's acting desperately
so it doesn't look that way
You know?
How long
I may be in this body
The more you treat it kindly
The breakup just becomes cruel
If you go back
to the child's body
If I can't make the antidote
Are we still classmates?
Can I continue to live a normal life?
continue
Haibara?
OK
Even if you can’t make an antidote
After 10 years, you will find that
seventeen columns are twenty-seven
Both of them are not kids
Surely you will overcome
your age and fall in love
So rest assured
Idiot
How do you know what's going on later?
I'm not sure but I
I won't give up hope
Must come back to this body
It will destroy the black tissue.
Do you want to avenge your sister's enemies?
Yes
The killer took risks
and moved the body.
What?
What keeps taking
Damn it
Why now
I borrowed the previous video
Show me quickly
This is the feeling of difference I felt at that time
But then those five people
Kudo?
Right
Maybe that's why the killer...
And I found out the identity
of another sense of difference
But there's one more thing you don't know
Damn, no time
Shinichi?
Why is that, Shinichi
Nothing
It's not a face that's nothing
Why
Why aren't you
telling me anything?
Ran
I can't go back to
Conan in front of Ran.
Dig the trap first from here
I'll try to solve this case.
I knew the killer
Bring people together
Shinichi
Okay, I'll be back
I
I'll wait until
Shinichi tells you
I'll believe
Ran
Oh, what the hell
is it for this time?
If you go back in front of Ran, it's over.
Know
So you have to fix it quickly
Knowing the killer
-Really?
- Yeah
The killer is strapped
to the body on stage
Committed a terrible murder.
This is a planned murder
tailored to a blackmail letter.
Smell the scent
This
Yes, it is cigar scent
In this letter you are blooming
The sweet scent of a unique cigar
Soaked in
Daigo Miura
-Like that..
.-No way
The person who smokes a cigar
Get used to the smell
You wouldn't have noticed
Admit it
As soon as I became Miss Japeresque
Karen started to keep me away
Karen used me
But
I just wrote it
Did not kill
I hear excuses at the police station.
Inspector Megure
Daigo Miura
Arrested for murder
of Karen Kotobuki.
Wait a minute
I didn't kill, it's real
I didn't kill
Hey, please wait
Don't touch it with dirty hands
Go in quickly
Glad the killer was caught.
Really
Oh, Shinichi?
Also
You were the real culprit
Mr. Shoichi Amano
What do you mean?
The culprit is Miura, isn't it?
That's you
To capture the evidence that he is the real culprit
It was a trap that I made
Why am i?
A few minutes at
best without my alibi
If the murder scene is
here, you can be committed.
You're in trouble
after killing Karen here
I thought about strapping
the body for two reasons.
First reason
Made into a planned murder
tailored to a blackmail letter
To make the person who wrote it suspicious
And one more reason
To hide the real way of killing.
What if it's the real way?
Your purpose is
Not to hang the body
Was to drop the body.
Killed by beating
To hide the real way of killing
Concealing what you killed by hitting it?
Stop here
This is the first feeling
of disparity that I felt
Enlarge this place
There are areas where the hair sticks
to the scalp and does not sag down
Really
why?
It's blood
There are already scars here
The bleeding blood stuck
to the hair and hardened.
That’s why only part of
the head doesn’t sag down
Things fall
If it cracks there
Everyone has this crack
You're mistaken
for it just fell apart.
But this gold
This is the gold that was formed before it fell.
You use this illusion
I was trying to hide
the real way of killing.
Well, if you look closely at the
biological reaction of the wound
Is it a wound from alive?
I'll soon know if it's
a wound after death
You didn't have that knowledge
The location of the wound is in the left occipital region
If the killer who suddenly appeared
from behind hit you and killed you,
What are you doing!
The culprit is left-handed
You used your left hand now
FYI, the other four suspects
were all right-handed.
I also...
Are you right-handed
through correction?
But momentarily,
I use my left hand
like now
Being treated as a criminal for that
You said there was blood
on Karen's hair, right?
That means
Karen was murdered long
before the stage started.
I stayed with the staff
Besides, it's 8:45
Me and you were
looking here with Mimi.
Karen wasn't anywhere at that time.
-Isn't it?
- Yeah
If I really killed Karen here
Where was the body?
I was here
I just couldn't see
When I came to look for Karen
And after the incident
I felt when I came here
The identity of a strange sense of heterogeneity
That's the amount of this paint
Didn't you come here again?
Are you doing whatever you want again?
There were three rows of paint cans at that time.
But now it’s two lines
What are you talking about?
I moved it
Where the paint was originally
Over here
How is that
You take the paint out of this box
Karen's body was
temporarily hidden inside.
There can’t be a human
body in such a small box, right?
This box
I have three
These three boxes
Only one in the middle
Go in a little bit
In zigzag
So just looking at it
I can’t think there’s
a person inside
But if you bend the body
to the side and lay it down
Can hide
You
Karen's body is bent
to the side and laid
Take the paint out of
the box and make room
I put three over Karen's body.
Here it is
Karen's blood.
If you're so sure I'm the
culprit, show me the evidence.
Conclusive evidence
that I killed Karen
There was one part I didn't know
It's the weapon that killed Karen.
I wouldn't have time to throw it away
But she didn't know where to hide
So I deliberately
arrested Miura,
I reassured the real culprit.
Then, obviously, to dispose of the weapon
I thought I was going to a hidden place.
And you are trapped
This is the conclusive evidence
I didn't mean to kill
I just
What's the dragon?
No, I want to congratulate
Do not lie
Are you the one who sent the blackmail letter?
Aren't I jealous
of success alone?
Karen, we used to love each other
You still can't believe me
I can't believe it
Don't be puffed up
Your past is like
trash to me now
No, it's less than trash
It's really disgusting to
date someone like you.
Will you disappear?
Forever before me
There were times when we trusted each other
Nevertheless
Just because
Is even such a heart a lie?
Amano Shoichi
Arrested for murder
of Karen Kotobuki.
Thank you for helping me this time again
Shinichi, are you okay?
Huh
Rather, Lieutenant Megure.
This guy with another officer
-Damn it
.-Shinichi!
Inspector, we are ready.
I'm going now
That fool, whatever he wants...
If you look into all this
Stupid
I know there's no time for that
I was prepared for it
Lie already?
Is it when you hold the form?
How do you...
I'm a detective
Shinichi
no
I was scared because
someone was aiming at me
Are you aiming?
You weren't Shinichi's assistant?
-No, that's..
.-That's right
-I'm not an assistant
.-Hey
I'm the client who commissioned
a case with this person.
client?
Thanks to Shinichi, the criminal was caught,
The killer's colleague is at
the hotel to take revenge on me.
This person is just
covering me like that
How do you believe it?
Huh
Let's escape here anyway
I'll explain it later
Shinichi, are you okay?
It's weird from before
Sorry, I have a little fever
Go
Where are you?
top?  under?
Where do I go
I just called my dad
and told him the situation.
The police say they'll send
a helicopter to the rooftop.
Idiot!
Then the police who came to
rescue them also told them...
no
Ran, good job
Kudo
Now it's the limit
What does that mean?
Get on quickly
Shinichi, quickly
Sorry
Ran
Shinichi...
Kudo
I can’t go back to
Conan in front of Ran.
Get on quickly
It's a guy
Quickly
When the elevator moves,
they'll come after you
I'll remain and be the bait
No, we are going together
do not worry
I can't die
But if I die
then
Give it to Ran
I will be there forever
I'm still by my side
I won't tell you that
I believe we will meet again
Please take care of Ran
Haibara
Kudo
see you again
I'm a man, brother.
I don't know who it is
Looks like Sherry has a knight.
But where are women
If you use that man's body
Sherry will give up and show up.
I gotta get some time
until they run away
Hold up until then
Where are you
Damn, is the helicopter still
What are you doing,
it's natural to be locked
My head doesn't turn
This is the key to the victim's room.
Ran and Haibara would
have arrived on the rooftop.
Be judged
brother
The article is on the 20th floor.
Where to find
Find everything
There is not
I think I'm in this room
okay
Now, come out quickly, driver.
There's no place for you to run away anymore
Quietly
Kneel before our guns
Will it be?
what?
Damn it, it's not on
Can't you hear?
This sound
The police special forces I called
That's the sound of 20 helicopters.
what?
found!
Ran, I'll save you now!
what?  In terms of
Ran and the detective kid's
client said there must be a woman.
Is that a doctor's kid?
The detective brother is being chased.
Save it quickly!
Are you a detective kid?
Where, where?
In this room soon
About 50 crews will come
Giving up
You guys